_
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
_
When you examine the collision
of the electrons and photons
using relativistic kinematics...
_
Why is it blue?
It's always blue.
Are you looking for him,
my lovelies?
'Cause he's looking for you.
Did you hear his message? No?
If you have the skill, you
can go back and listen again.
Why is it blue?
It's always blue...
...follow the bus.
Follow the bus.
The yellow bus.
_
Wait!
Hello?
_
Salmon.
Her name is Salmon.
♪ I know you think
I'm a psychopath ♪
♪ A Democrat lurking in the dark ♪
♪ This sucks, I'm
the Kmart soda jerk ♪
♪ Cirque du trash,
I kept the stash ♪
♪ Of cocoa candy
straight from Japan ♪
♪ Hologram Anne, she
was never as near ♪
♪ I think you know what
I need to get by, by, by ♪
♪ Something for your ♪
- ♪ Mind ♪
♪ Something for your mind ♪
♪ Mind ♪
♪ Something for your ♪
♪ For your... ♪
♪ M-I, M-I ♪
♪ M-I-N-D ♪
♪ I know you think I'm a sociopath ♪
♪ My lovely prey, I'm a cliché ♪
♪ Make way, I'm in my Pepsi mood ♪
♪ Mama needs food,
how about a barbecue ♪
♪ For us, the bourgeoisie ♪
♪ So carefree ♪
♪ Remember when we? ♪
♪ I don't know what ♪
♪ You need to get by ♪
- ♪ Something for your mind ♪
- ♪ Mind ♪
♪ Mind ♪
- ♪ Something for your mind ♪
- ♪ Mind ♪
♪ Mind ♪
- ♪ Something for your ♪
♪ For your, for your ♪
♪ For your ♪
♪ M-I, M-I... ♪
Far out. You're just in time.
Come on.
We've been waiting for you.
For me?
For everyone.
But especially you.
Where is this place?
I'm not sure.
My queen brought me here,
she of the frosted breakfast flakes.
We're gonna have a baby.
What is that?
Peace. Love.
He makes it. In here.
He's the Dream-Come-True-Man.
His thoughts are magic.
It's prayers mixed with dreams.
His spirit is the music
and the word.
What did it mean, "Don't
trust the mustache"?
And who's the basket?
And what are the forces
of multiplication?
Soon. He'll tell you everything.
But you're not ready yet.
Your mind has to open...
like a flower.
It takes time.
Do you know that word?
"Time"?
That's Squirrel.
He's the alchemist.
Greetings, earthlings.
Like your vibe.
Very two days from now.
Jia-yi.
No. That's not it.
We shall call you...
Switch.
And Switch
shall be your name.
Are you really a virgin?
Penis-free, 25 years.
This is where you wait.
She'll be here soon.
She?
"S" before "H."
My beloved,
the master of disaster.
- Her majesty.
- The breakfast queen.
Sorry for the wait.
Was it awful?
Not too bad.
So...
sad runaway
or spoiled daddy's girl?
Is this a cult?
Yes.
Are you the leader?
I'm Lenny.
And you are?
Switch.
Switch-hitter.
Do you swing?
I like boys.
Why?
Okay.
Never mind.
What do you want, Switcheroo?
A Band-Aid for your boo-boo?
I'm not looking for you.
You're looking for me.
"Are you a time traveler?
The forces of multiplication need you."
Prove it.
Not to you.
To him.
Hi.
I'm David.
Come on in.
I'll make some tea.
What is this place?
People have their pain.
Their hearts are sad.
Their minds are tired.
I help them.
How?
I'm the magic man.
All I ask
is that they stay and
keep me company after.
Take care of the house.
Love each other.
I need that.
Love.
How is this here?
This... cave?
I made it.
Try this.
Close your eyes.
And picture your bedroom.
Your bed.
Can you see it?
Really see it?
The walls, the windows?
The way the light falls?
Open your eyes.
It's a mental space.
You imagined it. I made it real.
You read my mind?
No secrets.
That's one of our rules.
What about trust?
Mm. I tried that,
and it's better to read people's minds.
I'm adopted.
When I was a baby,
a monster snuck into my head
and haunted me for 33 years.
But I'm better now.
How are you?
Good. I'm good.
You know. Fine.
How are you?
My dad collects robots.
Robotto.
There's a room in our apartment.
Some are life-sized.
Some toys.
Hundreds.
Sometimes at night, I go in there.
I stand very still,
and pretend I'm a robot, too.
So what are "the forces of division"?
Why do you need a time traveler?
So it's a girl thing.
You want to go back in time and... what?
Get your girlfriend back?
I thought about it.
Doing everything again, making
different choices, but...
...it won't work.
You know how sometimes you can
be so sure what the problem is
and then you realize the
problem is really something else?
No.
Oh. Well, you're young.
When I was in the psych ward,
everybody was so sure the
problem was neurological.
Brain chemistry, serotonin.
"David Haller, schizophrenic."
You were in a psychiatric hospital?
Oh. Oh. Lots of times.
Psych hospitals, emergency rooms.
"David, don't swallow all
your mother's diet pills."
"David, don't huff the
chemicals under the sink."
Like I'm supposed to... what?
Pretend the voices
aren't real? You know?
- Yeah, sure.
- You see, like I said,
when I was a baby, a
monster came into my head
and haunted me for, like, 33 years.
By "monster," you mean,
like, a metaphor, right?
Amahl Farouk. The Shadow King.
My dad, my real dad,
he kicked Farouk out of his
body into the astral plane.
And then he found me... Farouk...
and he moved in.
More tea?
I still don't know why
you need a time traveler.
To go back in time.
What else?
- How far?
- Well, how far can you go?
Stay down, kid.
_
- Her majesty...
- The breakfast queen.
Prove it.
To him.
I'm David.
Come on in.
I'll make some tea.
Yes, it pays to be kind.
Are you out of your mind?
"Is black tea okay?" What are
you gonna do with this one?
Give her a wee nib of the blue stuff
and sling her in with all the others?
Shall we sit out here?
I'm excited to talk to you,
hear what brought you to us.
We don't have time for that.
Lenny says you grew up in the city.
They're coming.
The forces of division.
They're almost here.
I've seen them.
They kill you.
No. I'd hear them.
You didn't last time.
What do you mean, "last time"?
"Time traveler wanted."
You wrote that.
"Find the pregnant virgin."
Well, I did. I'm here.
And we got to go...
Oh, David!
Stick with me.
Come on.
David!
This way!
You're cheating.
A time traveler.
C'est magnifique.
I had relations with
a time traveler once.
Geraldine.
Is it true that you are always women?
Pourquoi?
Maybe it has something
to do with regret.
Choices made and not made.
Opportunities missed.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Wherever this is.
This is...
the astral plane.
A world beyond the world.
Made of pure energy.
Very few can see it.
David, for example.
Oh, you know him.
David Haller.
He used to be easy to find.
His power was so loud
and no control.
But now...
Is this a...
mental space?
Did you make this?
I was looking for David...
and saw you.
Your... trail.
See?
The realms of time and space...
collide here in the plane.
Now...
the first time I see you,
I think, "Interesting."
But the second time...
You're helping him, no?
I don't know what you're talking about.
We, too, want to help him.
He's a very sick young man.
Then why did she shoot him?
The blonde?
You have seen this?
So we find him...
and you go back to change what happens.
- I have to go.
- To warn him.
What does he have that you need?
Maybe we can make a
different arrangement.
Tell me.
Why are you helping him?
_
Ah...
Time to symbiosis T-minus 45.
- I'm hungry.
- Not now.
That's right, I forgot
you're making a person.
It's not a person.
It's a fully synthetic
bipedal quantum computer.
Yeah, but it looks a lot
like somebody we know.
Initiating cranial fusion.
Time to symbiosis...
...T-minus 30.
Why does he have a mustache?
I don't know, I...
Time to symbiosis, T-minus 15.
Calibrating synchronicity.
Beginning data transfer.
Sentience in ten...
nine...
eight...
seven...
- six...
- Wonder if he'll still be grouchy.
- Shh.
- ...five...
four...
three...
two...
- One.
- Whoa.
It's, it's, it's all right.
Symbiosis complete.
The mainframe is now ambulatory.
How do you feel?
Running diagnostics.
Faulty HVAC unit in the Oslo facility.
Data slowdown in the Minsk network.
There are currently
nine faulty satellites
- in the atmospheric array.
- I meant you.
How do you feel?
You, the entity known as Ptonomy?
There is no Ptonomy, there
is only the mainframe.
Why do I have a mustache?
Oh, they have mustaches,
I just thought...
Routing all command
functions to this vessel.
Can we eat now?
In a moment. I have
to test his reflexes.
Slow.
Oh...
Not sure how much more
money we can throw at this.
You know, there are other threats.
He destroys the world.
I said that, right?
It's not... me.
I've got bosses and they've got bosses.
Well, I thought I was your boss.
Only at home.
He has a time traveler.
Who?
David.
I met her in the astral plane.
Uh, what do you mean,
he has a time traveler?
She's young, a teenager.
She has skill.
She's with David? How do you know?
We spoke.
So you had her... and
then you let her go?
Like I said, she has skill.
You see,
the astral plane exists at the crux
of time and space.
It's, uh, how do you say, um...
a rest stop.
I was able to intercept her, but only...
for a moment.
So where is he?
_
Our boy shields his mind from me.
And how does she help him?
This time traveler?
To answer, I must ask...
how do you surprise someone
who can go back in
time and warn himself?
Why don't we have a time traveler?
David Haller location detected.
That's industrial, low density.
I say we scramble the
jet and we drop a bomb.
No, no, it should be a team.
We've got to make sure.
You've trained for this.
And the time traveler?
Remember: whatever we do...
she can undo.
Great. Then we kill her, too.
We have him.
I'll get ready.
How big is the team?
You don't have to go.
I'm going.
Why not stay back?
Let us take care of things.
He's not my first boyfriend.
He's not even the first
boy to take advantage.
There's a job to do.
Revenge is not a job.
It's not that.
All that love, it
doesn't just disappear.
It must be transformed into an emotion
of equal intensity.
That is the law of the universe.
Pretty sure you're making that up.
My dear,
I am over 2,000 years old.
I don't make things up.
I have wisdom.
And my wisdom says you remain here
and we will kill him.
No.
I have to be there.
This should block your brain waves.
I've built similar tech into
our fighting friends' helmets.
This way, David won't hear us coming.
The David Haller phenomenon is contained
within normal space and time.
Outward signs indicate he
is unaware of our approach.
Probability of success?
67%.
Air support?
At the weigh station, ready to move in.
Spread out.
Clark.
I see him.
Get the hook.
Get ready to move.
Send in air support.
We go in ten,
nine,
eight, seven,
six,
five...
...four...
Ground connection lost.
Ground connection...
What's up?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --